# Front-end Developer

## Niloofar Arazkhani

Address: Iran, Tehran | Phone: (+98)9127829193 | Email: arazkhanin@gmail.com

Profile: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/niloofar-arazkhani-1581025b/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/niloofar-arazkhani-1581025b/</a> | Website:

https://niloofararazkhani.netlify.app

# **SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS**

A Front-end developer with good experience in software engineering, who loves building user-friendly platforms to present the rest of the team's work in an attractive way. With a strong curiosity for web technologies, I am always learning new skills and investigating new methods and tools for solving problems. Over 4 years of experience maximizing the potential of teams in both large companies and startups.

## **SKILLS**

+4 years experience: JavaScript | HTML | CSS | React

Others: Redux | Redux-thunk | Redux-saga | Redux toolkit | Mobx | TypeScript |
Next.js | styled-components | Sass | CSS-modules | Storybook | Jest | Cypress |
React-testing-library | Axios | Restful-APIs | Webpack | CI/CD | Linux | Git source
control | Agile | Scrum | system design

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

May 2022 - PRESENT(4mos)

Front-end Senior Developer - SnappExpress

SnapExpress is the leading online supermarket ordering company in Iran, a venture of Rocket Internet Group.

- Working as a solo front-end developer on two teams of more than 10 members.
- Develop features and maintain the mobile applications with more than 1000+ users using JavaScript, React, Redux-Saga
- Refactor parts of the code and improve the readability and performance of the project.

Aug 2021 - May 2022(11mos)

Front-end Developer - DigiExpress

DigiExpress is the leading online delivery company in Iran, a venture of Digikala.

- Improve delivery time by 24% through the development and enhancement of a new delivery application.
- Through the use of end-to-end testing by Cypress and unit testing by Jest, the company reduced the cost of the test by **20**%.
- Implementing an evaluation panel for our company with **50+** users to evaluate their own works for promotion.

Aug 2018 - Aug 2021(3 yrs)

#### Front-end Developer - Snappfood

Snapp Food is the leading online food ordering company in Iran, a venture of Rocket Internet Group.

- applying new features for expanding the company services which lead to 50% profits for the company.
- Refactoring and maintaining the old codes improved the user experience by 32%.
- Contributing to an integrated design system (using storybook) for projects in the company, accelerating productivity by around 38%

## **Education**

Sep 2016 - 2018

Amirkabir University, Tehran, Iran - Master (Computer Science)

Sep 2011 - 2015

Amirkabir University, Tehran, Iran - Bachelor (Computer Science)

## **Volunteer Works**

**Executive Committee Member, Persian Online Platform** - *persia* 7S

PersiaJS is a coding boot camp focused on web development in Persian.

#### Front-end Team Lead, Sharif University - DataDays

DataDays is a yearly Data challenge in first-rank universities of Iran.

## Languages

• English: Advanced Level (TOEFL 83)

• Persian: Native

• French: Intermediate (a2)

### **Hobbies**

Music | Books | Photography | Writing | Running | Travel